<!--
 ~ Copyright (c) 2005-2010, WSO2 Inc. (http://www.wso2.org) All Rights Reserved.
 ~
 ~ WSO2 Inc. licenses this file to you under the Apache License,
 ~ Version 2.0 (the "License"); you may not use this file except
 ~ in compliance with the License.
 ~ You may obtain a copy of the License at
 ~
 ~    http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
 ~
 ~ Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing,
 ~ software distributed under the License is distributed on an
 ~ "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY
 ~ KIND, either express or implied.  See the License for the
 ~ specific language governing permissions and limitations
 ~ under the License.
 -->

<!--
   refer following example to access parameters to put in the mail.
  -->
<configuration>
    <subject>You have been invited as a {roles} of {applicationId} Application</subject>
    <body>
Hi {userName},

Welcome to {applicationName} Application as a {roles}.
    {applicationName}:
    {applicationDescription}
    {roleTask}
    You can access your application through https://appfactorypreview.wso2.com/appmgt/site/pages/application.jag?applicationName={applicationNameEncoded}&amp;applicationKey={applicationId}

Thank you
    </body>
    <userParams>
        <roleTask>
                <developer>
    As a Developer, you need to checkout the application from the repository URL and import the project to your preferred IDE.
    You can add your implementation and commit the code again to the repository.Once committed, you can build the code. Once built, you can deploy and launch your application.
    If you need to check the logs of the developed application, you have the facility of downloading the logs.
    Once you are done with the development of the application, you can promote the application into the QA stage
        </developer>
                <qa>
    As a QA, you can launch the Application hosted in the test environment and perform functional and non functional testing.
    Once the necessary tests are completed, you can promote the application to Staging environment.
    Once you are done with the testing, you can promote the application to the Staging environment
                </qa>
                <devOps>
    As a DevOp, you can check the staging environment, do the necessary production database and other resource configurations and promote the application to the Production environment.
                </devOps>
        </roleTask>
    </userParams>
</configuration>

